So as you see my profile photo is shown over here. This means that I am logged in to my account
And it says what are you working on today? Grammar checker. So these are all the tools that quillbot provides us with, right?
So we can have an AI detector. So it's very cool. Let's actually do that. Let's
Let me sign into my chat GPT account over here. Let's say that. Okay
Hello, chat GPT. I want you to generate me a pretty
long article about how to start
with learning French as a
foreign nerve
Let's do this. And I want to get an article over here. So I can
Do some actions in quillbots on it. So yes
As you see
It's making it pretty long as I request it, but it's a little bit too long, right?
Come on
Okay, it's actually a lot. But whatever
so
Learn French as a foreigner
But you to online I can create also create. Okay. I copied this entire article
I copy it and I come to quillbots